Well, let's see, before I started
bueno a ver quería yo antes de comenzar
training, I wanted to
con el entrenamiento quería yo
react to a couple of things, so how are we
reaccionar a un par de cosillas entonces
not going to react to a couple of
como no vamos a reaccionar a un par de
things about
cosillas de
plans for how we are going to relate to
planes en cómo nos vamos a relacionar a
the entire range? Well, he ran a
la gama entera pues él corrió aquí un
video here, I don't know if I would have gotten it right because I haven't
vídeo no sé si habría acertado porque no
seen absolutely anything. I saw
he visto absolutamente nada he visto
a video here of the best moments, okay,
aquí un vídeo de mejores momentos vale
epic entries, prizes, and outfits, okay,
entradas épicas premios y outfits vale
if we don't have enough here with the
si no tenemos aquí suficiente con los
outfits, we have a brand article here
outfits tenemos aquí un artículo de
in which I think all the
marca en el que creo que están todos los
outfits are, okay, so let's go to them,
outfits vale así que vamos a ellos
family, let's see the best moments
familia vamos a ver los mejores momentos
and let's see how
y a ver qué tal
it goes. It goes very well, the best plays very well.
eso va muy bien toca muy bien el mejor
I think it's going too far for my taste, I
yo creo que va demasiado para mi gusto o
mean, I see more of a little thing like the M of the
sea yo veo más una cosita como el m de
show or like, for example, it was Jordi
show o como por ejemplo fue el jordi
While who will come out now, who will be on Friday,
while que saldrá ahora quien el viernes
but I am there, I have done it, I see it, a wedding suit,
pero yo esté lo he hecho lo veo traje de
this is the wedding suit, I don't see it
esto es lo del traje de boda no lo veo
for one, for the
para una para el evento
tenth event, a little thing like that, and you know, one
decimario una cosita así y sabes una
thing without water, I
cosa sin agua
don't see the point of this, I
esto no le veo sentido a esto
don't see the point of this,
esto no le veo sentido
everyone can go however they want, for the
cada uno puede ir como quiera por
first time that I am live, greetings
primera vez que estoy en directo saludos
to everyone  a hug now thank you very much
a todos un abrazos ahora muchas gracias
to people of 40 years old and then let's see that
a gente de 40 años y entonces a ver que
each one can go as they want or well of
cada uno puede ir como quieran o bien de
project it seems to me to go disguised a little
proyecto me parece ir disfrazado un poco
no
no
[Music] very
[Música]
handsome very handsome
guapísimos guapísimos
very handsome the thing of the much cloth no look that has a cool roll that I don't dislike when the photo the psuv as he normally dresses in his style I don't dislike but this thing of the blogs and addresses kripper for the truth and disguised thank you miss thank you very much it
disfrazado gracias señorita muchas
seems good
me parece bueno
horrible it is horrible horrible horrible the
horrible es horrible horrible horrible
most beautiful the most beautiful the
la más guapa la más guapa
most beautiful
la más guapa
what are you doing
qué haces
[Music]
[Música]
welcome
bienvenido
that about the clip but not to
que sobre lo del clip pero tampoco para
take it so seriously let's see if it is to be
tomárselo tan en serio a ver si es para
taken seriously of course you have to know how to
tomarse en serio claro hay que saber
be in the places no no it
estar en los sitios no
is
está
wrong
equivocado
the belt appears that he is disguised
el cinturón se aparece que va disfrazado
it seems that he is a child who went down to the
parece que es un niño que bajaba al
park in the afternoon or rather I for example did
parque por la tarde o sea yo por ejemplo
not have what I
no tenía
tell you I
a eso de que te digo yo
5 or 6 years things and I went down to the
5 o 6 años cosas y yo me bajaba a la
street and also that I had the neighborhood even
calle y además que tenía el barrio hasta
to all the people of the neighborhood up to the
a toda la gente del barrio hasta los
balls  no because i would walk down the street
[__] no porque yo me bajaba la calle
half like superman and i would walk down dressed as
medio por superman y bajaba vestido de
superman but of course not dressed as
superman pero claro no vestido de
superman with a power suit a
superman con un traje potente un disfraz
nice costume no no no
guapo no no no
blue pajamas or blue pajamas and some
un pijama azul o pijama azul y unos
red underwear outside the pajamas
calzoncillos rojo por fuera del pijama
okay and now i would hide
vale y ahora yo me dedicaba a esconderme
in every corner of the parking lot
por todas las esquinas del aparcamiento
below my house and every time
de abajo de mi casa y cada vez que
a man or a woman passed by
pasaba algún señor o alguna señora
[ __ ] 20 from here we don't know
[__] 20 de aquí no se sabe
and Taiwan when you're a kid you like
y taiwán cuando eres chico que te gusta
that you're into all the new things and you
que estás con todas las novedades y te
put them on at the same time like a
las pones a la vez en plan una camiseta
super mario t-shirt some mickey
de supermario un pantalón de mickey
mouse pants and a donald duck belt and you
mouse y un cinturón del pato donald y te
put it all on at once because you
lo pones todo a la vez porque todo te
like everything a lot and even though it didn't penetrate well that's what it did I mean
gusta mucho y aunque no penetró pues eso
this belt
es lo que ha hecho o sea este cinturón
with this sweatshirt with it with this cap
con esta sudadera con él con esta gorra
it borders it seems like the cap appears to be one
la bordea parece es que la gorra aparece
of those bad caps that they give you at
de estas gorras malas que te regalan en
the gas station I
la gasolinera
fight for today they'll do serious rock words what have you
peleo por hoy harán serio rock words lo
come to have a good time like
que habéis venido a pasarlo bien como
we are welcome to the
estamos seáis bienvenidos a los premios
slam awards when right now I can't believe I
slam cuando ya ahora mismo no me creo
'm here I believe it  there are a lot of
que estoy aquí lo creo que hay un montón
people behind me I can't do
de gente detrás mío yo no puedo hacer
this without saying hello hello guys how are
esto sin saludarlos hola chavales cómo
we
estamos
[Applause] I
[Aplausos]
did it very well in your style
lo he hecho capaz muy bien a su estilo
the shoes what I don't like the truth is
los zapatos lo que no me gusta la verdad
the suit
el traje
well a little old fashioned to my taste
bueno un poco anticuado a mi gusto
Vicente thank you very much but nothing for him
vicente muchas gracias pero nada para él
for good I don't like the shoes
para bien los zapatos no me gustan
thank you very much to all of you who are
muchas gracias a todos los que estáis
watching the stream and well I hope it's
viendo el stream y bueno espero que sea
a good night for all of us who
una buena noche para todos los que
are here especially for me I have
estamos aquí especialmente para mí yo he
come to win and to compete in everything
venido a ganar y a competir en todo lo
you can it's difficult when you
que puedas es que es [__] cuando
compete against the best Jordi Bienes
compites contra los mejores jordi bienes
also and now it's going to go great
además y ahora irá estupendamente
this is the roll of I like this is how
este es el rollo de me gusta así es como
I would be a trend more than ever
yo iría siendo tendencia más que nunca
although he and
si bien él y
I are going to call me a party pooper or
yo me vais a llamar aguafiestas o
bitter or whatever okay but the thing about
amargado o lo que sea vale pero lo de lo
the joke now from mister since
de la gracia ahora de míster ya que esté
the joke of gay misery and these things is in fashion I
de moda el chiste de miseria gay y estas
don't understand it then it's that
cosas no lo entiendo entonces es que
I am very bomber because this mind they have
estoy muy bomber porque esta mente
my age since in will be my age
tienen mi edad ya que en tendrá mi edad
or older you know but why does he go with this in his
o más sabes pero porque va con esto en
mouth and with that necklace and what's the
la boca y con ese collar y cuál es el
joke
chiste
these people  of the group made when he decides to
esta gente del grupo hecho cuando le da
take someone as a meme and as if it
por [__] a alguien como meme y como si
were a joke that is not funny man
fuera una gracia que no tiene gracia tío
what happens more not being able to you
lo que pasa más no poder
are already a misunderstood genius
ya eres un genio incomprendido
but you apply to me what is the joke of
pero me aplicáis cuál es la gracia de
a man well I am in Liberia ashamed he
que un señor pues yo a liberia vergüenza
invited me to a gala go with a
a mí me invitó a una gala ir con una
ball put in your mouth I would be ashamed do
bola mete en la boca me daría vergüenza
not try to understand it enjoy but
no trates de entenderlo disfruta pero
let's see the god
vamos a ver el dios
having heard this is normal
haber escuchado esto es normal
how about the thanks that he is crazy I have
qué tal con las gracias que está loco
doubts because I wanted to do
me nace la duda porque yo quería hacer
the interview but if you have that side
la entrevista pero si tienes ese lado
that I don't know if at that time of answering me you
que no sé si a esa hora de responderme
feel this event
sientes este evento
applause applause you know I am the
un aplauso un aplauso sabe yo soy el
interviewee and I would say
entrevistado y yo diría
take that out of your mouth please this
quita eso de la boca por favor esta
interview that I do not understand anymore Greece who is
entrevista que no entiendo ya grecia que
already 27 this man is 27 years old
ya tiene 27 este hombre tiene 27 años
see the only person who has a
ver la única persona que tiene una
category for himself
categoría para él solo
how did you live that moment that says do not
cómo lo viviste ese momento que dice no
look at the content creation awards
mira los premios de la creación de
a category that you take it for a hundred
contenido una categoría que por cien te
[Music]
[Música]
so
así
whatever it is the best to my 3
sea lo que sea lo mejor a mi hijo de 3
year old son thanks in fact seven thousand
años las gracias de hecho siete mil
five hundred euros of suits I would
quinientos euros de trajes
n't attempt at the highest level border
no intentaría al máximo nivel frontera
with the clock
con el reloj
really it's pure charade since I go to so
realmente es puro paripé como voy a tan
few things well it's cool at least to look
poquitas cosas pues mola por lo menos ir
good and well dressed is fine whoever looks
bien y bien vestida va bien el que vaya
bad but you don't
mal pero no me
have the opportunity there is
tienes la oportunidad
a part that I saw there is
hay una parte que vi
a part that I saw where they put the click
hay una parte que vi que ponían el clic
of Dario's punch m leche to Oslo
del puñetazo de darío m leche a oslo
like a tit at the gala I do
como un chiche en la gala
n't know if it will be put here in this summary
no sé si lo pondrá aquí en este resumen
but literally it is as if it were a joke
pero literal es como si fuera un chiste
it is to punch someone and
es pegar un puñetazo a alguien y
break a tooth
partirlo un diente
to attack someone literally to
para agredir a alguien literalmente
attack someone I am
agredir a alguien
going to give a gift
voy a hacer un regalo
no this is a filter a filter of I
no esto es un filtro un filtro de yo
internet or so that you do whatever you
internet o para que te hagas tú lo que
want the spectacular to everyone at
quieras la espectacular a todos los de
the gala
la gala
with it or not
con él o no
a filter so that they do whatever you
un filtro para que te hagan lo que
want to you let's
quieras
see there are the dark-skinned people to be party
a ver existen los morenos por ser
poopers or anything I understand that
aguafiestas ni nada yo entiendo que el
humor in humor but underlying humor as I
humor en el humor pero humor de fondo
already told you is the same I am a
que ya te digo es lo mismo soy yo un
little bitter about the same thing I am a little
poco amargado de lo mismo soy un poco
bitter but pot humor
amarga pero humor de porros
I do pot they are very bad
yo lo porro son malísimos
very bad and  the worst thing there is
malísimos y lo peor que hay
tells me when you do it when
me dice a mí cuando lo haces cuando
you're 15 14 16 years old that are in between and
tienes 15 años 14 16 que están medios y
lee polla wants to make you the huayno doesn't
lee [__] te quiere hacer el huayno no
want to make you feel left out because you
te quiere sentir desplazado porque no
're not in a group that does it and well
estás en un grupo que lo hace y bueno ya
since it was spent like why not smoke
que fue gastaba como porque no fumarse
a joint they should when but it leaves you an idiot it
un porro deben cuando pero te deja
leaves you an idiot and now that's
te deja [__] y ahora eso te va
killing your neurons
matando neuronas
the worst is the worst now that's killing your
lo peor es lo peor ya eso te va matando
neurons until
neuronas hasta que
[Music]
[Música]
okay there it will come I put it
vale ahí llegará lo pongo
okay air something whatever the neurons that
vale aire algo como sea las neuronas que
kill you the pores are totally
te maten los poros son totalmente
unrecoverable
irrecuperable
you understand it's not funny thanks to
me entiende no es gracioso gracias a las
drugs they are not funny it's not funny
drogas no son gracioso no es divertido
you understand
entendéis
there it is all drugs are bad but
ahí está todas las drogas son malas pero
there are some that are worse inhabit
hay algunas que son peores habitan
crystal no but it's not about
cristal no pero que no se trata de
crystal it's about recommending
cristal se trata de recomendar a la
something to people well that you have that
gente algo bien que tú tienes ese
problem that smokes weed well if you
problema que fuma porro bueno pues si tú
have that problem then do it in your
tienes ese problema pues hazlo tú en tu
[ __ ] house and don't do it and don't make it
[__] casa y no lo hagas y no se lo hagas
seem to your audience
ver a tu público
like a funny thing japo rosso
como una cosa divertida japo rosso
first when you're 40 years old
primero cuando tienes 40 años
each one defines their  limits of humor
cada uno define sus límites del humor
but let's normalize things like a few
pero que normalicemos cosas como unas
thanks well no let's
gracias pues no
normalize things like like a
que normalicemos cosas como la como una
joke alcohol jokes are okay well neither well neither but
gracia bromas de alcohol está bien
the joints are worse it's
peor los porros
worse the crystal joints that I
es que peor los porros a cristal que me
have to laugh that it's at a gala you get
tengo que reír de que es en una gala se
paid they give you a mouthpiece parcel
nómina te regala una boquilla paquetería
in whatever let's
en lo que sea
see it's not that I was scandalized that
a ver que no es que me escandalicé que
I get together with a lot of people who
yo me junto con un montón de gente que
smoke it that crystal energies and I was
lo fuman que energías a cristal y me
scandalized they don't scandalize me I
escandalicé no me escandalizan os
assure you that I will never get
aseguro que yo en la vida me voy a
analyzed from a joint I assure you
analizar de un porro os lo aseguro
campus thank you very much welcome king
campus muchas gracias bienvenido rey
or I assure you that it will be that I am
o aseguró que será que a mí me hace
missing many things very I would
muchas faltas cosas muy a mí me haría
need a lot of something very serious to
falta muchísima una cosa gravísima para
scandalize mommy
escandalizar mami
for youth and life and everything I
por la juventud y la vida y todo lo que
lived I guarantee it but I am already at
vivió yo os lo garantizo pero ya tengo
an age I already see it done it is a mouthpiece
una edad ya lo veo hecho es una boquilla
with the internet logo or a
con el logo del internet o lo hace un
kid makes it with 3d printing
chaval con impresión 3d
this kid is cool
este chaval va guay
that kid is doing super well but
ese chaval va súper bien pero
you lack street look surely  when you were
te falta calle mira seguramente cuando
born you had already lived life and knew
nacido ya había vivido la vida y sabía
everything there was to life, the one who
todo lo que era todo en la vida el que
apple with your comments you lack
apple con vuestros comentarios te falta
street smarts if you think you're cool because you see
calle que si te crees guay porque ves en
people on tweets who smoke weed or who
tweets a gente que fuma porro o que
make jokes about weed and that makes you
hacen chistes de porro y eso te hace
feel older, well congratulations, I'll
sentirte más mayor pues enhorabuena te
pat you on the back twice but I'm
doy dos palmaditas en la espalda pero yo
telling you that I don't think it's funny it
te digo a ti que no me parece una gracia
's a responsibility to do
es una responsabilidad
that and then there are people who are
que se haga eso y luego son gente que se
scandalized that they do promotions for
escandalicen de que se hagan promo de
betting houses you understand me I
casas de apuestas me entendéis
assure you don't tell me that
ya te aseguro que a mí no me digáis que
you lack street smarts precisely on my street it's
te falta calle precisamente a mi calle
just missing more too much for my
nomás falta más sobra demasiado para mi
taste more hours
gusto más horas
too much for my taste
demasiado para mi gusto
for bed please
para la cama por favor
argentina everywhere in the house
argentina en todos lados en la casa
greetings argentina in the house always today in
saludo argentina en la casa siempre hoy
front that he told me that he was
delante que me comentó que le estaba
giving him some type of liquor I don't know if it's
dando un tipo de licor no sé si es
reliable or not but he's a little
confiable o no pero lleva un poco
intoxicated maybe it's strip I'm not
entonado puede ser tira yo no llevo
intoxicated but we were drinking rum
entonado pero estuvimos tomando ron
well no I mean you can't go wrong
bueno no o sea no te puede quedar mal
never
nunca
crack in what we were drinking  very
crack en lo que veníamos tomando muy
good rum
buen ron
the one that's half bad is marquitos
el que está medio mal es marquitos
because marquitos hospital so the
porque marquitos nosocomio así que el
marquito is complicated take advantage of what
marquito está complicado aprovechen lo
the female brings how handsome that you
que trae la hembra qué guapo que os
lm that goes [ __ ] great she's talking about
lm eso va de [__] madre está hablando de
something that isn't there's
una cosa que no es
a clip of you saying hello
hay un clip tuyo diciendo hola
very good
buenísimo
thank you very much
muchas gracias
and there's no air in paula you are not
y no hay aire en paula no estáis
moderating the blog people like this who have
moderando blog la gente como este que ha
posted seven times the copy and paste the same thing
puesto siete veces el copia y pega igual
took me away kawaii that is not deleting the
me quitó kawaii eso es no borrar el
comment I am banned
comentario estoy baneado
those banned people like that caliber is
esos baneado gente así de ese calibre es
banned
baneado
by cable or I
por cable o
remove myself I don't know what yours has been
me quito no sé que vuestro lleva diez
posting the same copy and paste for ten minutes
minutos poniendo el mismo copia y pega
this is panning look and you get it
esto es paneo mira y lo obtienes a
through fabric put so you can
través de tela puesto para que lo puedas
way okay that is hiding user in the
manera vale eso es ocultar usuario en el
channel people like that have been banned in this
canal se han baneado gente así en este
channel already outside you understand me or rather I have
canal ya afuera me entiende o sea ya
never entered you know that I never
nunca me he metido a ya sabéis que nunca
ban in that I have never hidden a
baneo en que nunca ha ocultado
comment but from now on it
comentario pero ya a partir de ahora se
will be moderated
va a moderar
no no to 20 minutes and that no
no no a 20 minutos y eso no
that is already dizzy and everything that is hater
eso es ya mareo y todo lo que sea hater
in the channel that puts me [ __ ]
en el canal que me ponga gilipolleces de
for example when I've talked about milk
por ejemplo cuando he hablado de leche
from the strike of da the people who don't comment
del strike de da la gente que no comente
with respect and that are leave that hidden
con respeto y que sean deje eso oculta
in the channel and never comment again
en el canal y no comenta nunca más la
life for example today when the post I
vida por ejemplo hoy cuando el puesto he
made the video of the extra and of dalla via-
hecho el vídeo del extra y de dalla via-
people but justify this the one of nauta
gente pero justifica este el de nauta
hidden outside you can't comment on
ocultado fuera no puedes comentar en
this channel through all the videos
este canal mediante todos los vídeos
that I like that you can't see
that i like que no se ve
that paid attention to the wall only that
that hecho caso con la pared sólo que
during the nobody understands me dog from
durante la nadie me entiende perro de
dallas
dallas
hidden okay shut your mouths
ocultados vale cierren la boca que está
my father is talking exactly
hablando mi padre exactamente
exactly that he cries and that they get frustrated
exactamente que llore y que se frustren
with the wall only I understand myself
con la pared yo solo me entiende
and up to here we comment with respect all
y hasta aquí se comenta con respeto todo
the daily life of all the toilets without
el cotidiano de todos los aseos sin
disrespecting either the people in the chat
faltar el respeto ni a la gente del chat
or the people in the chat or the stream
ni a la gente del chat ni a los stream
is what we are talking about okay so that's
es de los que estamos hablando vale
why the chapas is open
entonces por eso el chapas está abierto
now because it will be able to be open
ahora porque se va a poder estar abierto
because the minimum that puts the prawn
porque el mínimo que meter la gamba
hidden point has
punto ocultado
not stopped putting the same thing all the
no ha parado de poner lo mismo todo el
time annika but it is that he will be a
rato annika pero es que será un crío de
78 year old kid that I continue internet or and las
78 años que siga yo internet o y las
heras travels by ross when that  kid
heras viaja por ross cuando ese chaval
still doesn't even know where children are born you'll have me they
todavía no sabe ni de dónde nacen los
are mentalities of kids who watch
son mentalidades de chavales que ven
youtuber that makes them grow like
youtuber que los hace crecer como
idiots
[__]
diaz for this event
díaz por este evento
very well very well put together I really liked
muy bien muy bien montado me ha gustado
the
la
cream
crema
let's look for it I'm going to look for it and I'll
vamos a buscarlo le voy a buscar y te lo
bring it to you yes but it has a very
traigo sí pero lleva un rollo muy
good vibe good for everyone the
bueno bueno para todo el mundo la
first entry honor is very bad for
primera entrada honor es muy malo para
me it is an honor to be here at the canario
mí es un honor estar aquí en el canario
david first entry of our
david primera entrada de nuestros
awards there was desire or that there is a lot it
premios había ganas o que haya mucho
seems like a reggaeton singer papi
parece un cantante de reggaeton el papi
gabino no nothing it's going well it's going well it's going well it's
gabino no nada va bien va bien va bien
handsome the desire you like the idea it
va guapo la gana te gusta la idea
's not normal to see forgive but tell me
no es normal ver a perdonar pero diga
but seeing them is not normal
pero lo de verlos no es normal
I respect
yo respeto
[Music]
[Música]
reminds me of my hater moments
me recuerda mis momentos de hater
with you javi and yet they
contigo javi y sin embargo siempre
were always very respectful with me I'm glad to have
fueron muy respetuosos conmigo me alegro
rectified that laughing with
de haber rectificado aquel riendo con
glasses thank you region thank you very much here
gafas gracias región muchas gracias aquí
the salsa singer is going to go in a
ya el salsero va a ir de una forma
different way we are giving the channel a beating
diferente le estamos dando una caña al
impressive but already garbage and
canal impresionante pero ya basura y
toxicity and that [ __ ] here is not going to be
toxicidad y esas [__] aquí no se va a
allowed here I know gossip is talked about
permitir aquí sé cotillea se habla de
the al  62 the controversy with all due
los al 62 la polémica con todo el
respect and a minimum of little garbage and
respeto y el mínimo de poca basura y
disrespect and those girls to all
falta de respeto y esas niñas a todos
these disgusting people of this type because those who
estos asquerosos de este tipo porque los
have appeared and in the cha when
que han aparecido y en el cha cuando
we have mentioned the internet or that
hemos mencionado del internet o que
objectively objectively
objetivamente
totally criticizable that
objetivamente totalmente criticable que
a person in a program or just as it
una persona en un programa o sea igual
seems totally criticizable and
que me parece totalmente criticable y
regrettable to me that in a program in a
lamentable que en un programa en un
podcast that has thousands or tens of
podcast que tiene miles o decenas de
thousands of viewers a
miles de espectadores se le agrega a un
partner is added or rather one of the presenters
compañero o sea uno de los presentadores
adds the other and is treated like a baby
agrega al otro y se trate como un bebé
okay that it is treated like a meme that it is
vale que se trate como un meme que se
treated like a joke
trate como una gracia
[Music]
[Música]
and that on top of that there are brands making memes
y que encima haya marcas haciendo meme
with that well it seems equally criticizable to me
con eso pues igual de criticable me
that they appear in a gala of this
parece que aparezcan en una gala de esto
and look he gave you a mouthpiece and they make
y mira te regaló una boquilla y se hagan
jokes about joints or crystal or anything I
chistes de porros ni cristal ni nada yo
can guarantee that I have seen
puedo garantizar que yo habéis visto
photos of me when I was young I can guarantee
fotos mías de joven yo puedo garantizar
that things like that do not scare me on the
que a mí cosas de esas no me asustan al
contrary
contrario
now at 36 years old or I can say that I look
ya con 36 años o puedo decir que miro
back
atrás
that I look at myself when I was 18 years old and
que me miro a mí cuando tenía 18 años y
the brave [ __ ] what the [ __ ]
los valientes [__] que [__] te
should have given you your  father in the
tenía que haber dado tu padre en toda la
mouth
boca
really the things that you do
de verdad las cosas que ustedes hacen
thanks to the kids that I am a fan of the
gracias a los niñatos que soy fan de los
youtube offend and they put those things or
youtube ofender y os ponen esas cosas o
give and shame well we are going to be
dar y vergüenza bueno nos va a dar
ashamed ask ourselves I am public you are
vergüenza preguntarnos soy público usted
not going to see your own
no vais a ver vuestros propios
comments in 20 years but you
comentarios dentro de 20 años pero os
will be ashamed and you will understand and how
daréis vergüenza y lo entenderéis y qué
right was Xavi how ashamed I am what
razón tenía xavi que vergüenza doy que
fools am I going to be
tontos voy a soy
offended I do not take offense I find it
yo ofenderme no me ofendo me parece
regrettable
lamentable
precisely because you like
precisamente porque tú te gustan los
challenges and those that until today are a
retos y esos que hasta para hoy es
member exactly do not do it to you for what
miembro exactamente no te lo hacen por
other members do not and literally
lo hace otros miembros no y literalmente
if they do not do it to you because you spend everything on
si no te lo hacen por lo gasta todo en
subscriptions of have favorite whatever or
suscripciones de tienen favorito sea o
whatever
sea
you have a problem that you were a
que tú tienes un problema que tú fueras
pothead because you are addicted to potheads
porro porque estás enganchado los porros
or because there are people who are addicted to
o porque hay gente que está enganchada a
potheads and if not you do not sleep if you do not
los porros y si no no duerme si no se
smoke a joint well okay
fuma un porro bueno vale
I think that everything is a matter of mind sami
yo creo que todo es cosa de mente sami
suddenly you know suddenly it
de repente ya lo sabéis de repente se me
occurred to me to stop smoking tobacco and I did it you will
ocurrió dejar de fumar tabaco y lo hice
see how I have improved how it will
si veréis como he mejorado cómo va a
improve the health I can go up down the
mejorar la salud puedo subir bajar la
stairs [ __ ] great I
escalera de [__] madre
carry the shopping  from the child's carriage to the
subo la compra del carro del niño al
child to my wife to my grandmother in my arms
niño a mi mujer a mi abuela en brazos
down the stairs to a fifth floor and a new
por las escaleras a un quinto y nueva
hobby and literally I don't get heartburn anymore you don't
afición y literales ya no me dan ardores
give me any burning sensation nothing
no me das ardentía no me sienta mal nada
to eat makes me feel bad you don't know how life changes
de comer no sabéis lo que cambia la vida
drugs all drugs are terrible
drogas todas las drogas son malísimas
there are more and less you can tell from your voice that
hay más y menos se nota en la voz que
many times I'm speechless there are
muchas veces me queda sin habla
drugs in ban - it's not that
hay drogas en baní - no es que el
alcohol asem in the end it's the mentality
alcohol asem al final es la mentalidad
of someone who now well all that who will be
del que ahora pues todo eso que tendrá
15 or 14 years old it's not that alcohol every
15 años o 14 años no es que el alcohol a
week it's that it's not about lying down you
semana es que no se trata de tumbado tú
- it's about not inciting or treating it
- se trata de que no incite o lo trate
like a joke nothing listen that one day
como una gracia nada oye que yo un día
here I have a beer well then I
aquí me tomo una cerveza bueno pues me
have a beer
tomo una cerveza
because I am responsible for saying or I mean
porque yo soy responsable de decir o sea
look a beer who has a
pues mira una cerveza que toma una
beer I can have a beer
cerveza yo me puedo tomar una cerveza
every month or every two months a
cada mes o cada dos meses de una
little drink on special occasions
copichuela en las ocasiones especiales
what does it do bad well it's different damage to
qué hace mal bueno es diferente daño a
other things different what happens like
otras cosas diferente lo que pasa como
for example with joints is what
por ejemplo con los porros es a lo que
I was referring to it is irreparable damage
yo me refería que es un daño irreparable
there are other drugs that do you a
hay otras drogas que te hacen un daño
more or less repairable damage that the body
más o menos reparables que el cuerpo se
regenerates whatever it is worth that
vuelve a regenerar lo que sea vale esa
part of the body that is affected can be
parte del cuerpo que es afecta se puede
improved you can treat whatever but
mejorar se puede tratar lo que sea pero
the damage from joints is completely
el daño de los porro es completamente
irreparable and when you're 40 years old and
irreparable y cuando tengas 40 años y
you talk like an idiot
hables como un [__]
and you can't relate to people who
y no te puedas relacionar con gente que
aren't the ones in the square below
no sean los de la plazoleta de abajo de
your house then you'll be ashamed
tu casa pues entonces te darás vergüenza
and you'll remember what
y te acordarás de lo que te está
javi oliveira is telling you you
diciendo javi oliveira
understand me and I'm not going to say if
me entendéis y no voy a decir si el
alcohol does more or less that I'm not a
alcohol hace más o menos de que no soy
doctor I don't understand but I can guarantee
médico no entiendo pero puedo garantizar
that I know people who have smoked for
que conozco gente que fuma por los desde
20 30 30 years and you listen to them talk and I
20 30 30 años y tú los escucha hablar y
tell them
les digo
and they embarrass me
y me dan vergüenza
because they don't connect one sentence with the other
porque no conectan una frase con la otra
well and they tell you things that are not
bien y te dicen unas cosas que no no son
intelligent
inteligentes
you know what you have to exercise and what you have to get
sabéis lo que hay que ejercitar y a lo
hooked on reading watching
que te tienes que enganchar a leer a ver
documentaries informing yourself about things to
documentales a informarte de las cosas a
things that you upload guy
cosas que te suben tío
understands me and that's it and if there's someone
me entiende y ya está y si hay alguien
who doesn't understand because they watch their
que no lo entiende porque ve a su
youtube that ha ha ha ha humor then no no  it's
youtube que ja ja ja ja humor pues no no
funny and I respect those who smoke it
es gracioso y yo respeto al que lo fume
okay doesn't respect those who don't smoke I
vale no respeta al que no fume que
knew a lot of people who smoked but I didn't
conocí a mucha gente que fumado pero no
treat it on the internet my audience as
lo trató en internet mi audiencia como
if it were a joke just that
si fuera una gracia simplemente eso que
you smoke it other way forms the perfect
tú te lo fuma tro forma el perfecto
but I didn't try to understand how it's
pero no trate de entender cómo que es
funny and how making a
gracioso y como haciendo una
normalization of avalanches
normalización de aludes
in my opinion if
en mi opinión
the video has been left and
sí ha quedado el vídeo y aparece
cerati appears it doesn't mean that he wants his
cerati no quiere decir que quiere su
friend for me we would all have to
amigo para mí tendríamos que todos
do a 32 13 21 h okay but how
hacemos un 32 13 21 h vale pero como
would they be like that you can interpret it nobody
serían así lo podéis interpretar nadie
is perfect perfect come on let's do it
es perfecto perfecto vamos vamos a hacer
guys and honestly I respect
los chicos y sinceramente que yo respeto
my orlov macayo well always the whole
a mi orlov macayo bien siempre todo el
thing but we are criticizing we are not
rollo pero estamos criticando no estamos
here to criticize each other so you
aquí para criticarnos entonces ustedes
give the same impression you give it gives the
da la misma impresión ustedes dan os da
same the same bearing and it gives you the same
la misma el mismo porte y os da la misma
impression gref I love how it goes I
impresión gref que me encanta cómo va me
love how it's going to give the same impression in
encanta cómo va a dar la misma impresión
fact that this
hecho que esto
gives you the same impression
os da la misma impresión
I ask
pregunto
or does it make the same difference it looks just as pretty
o da lo mismo se ve igual de bonito
he is the protagonist
él es el protagonista
but it still goes [ __ ] great
pero igual va de [__] madre
for you in sight at the palau de la
a ustedes a la vista en el palau de la
msica in barcelona man
música de barcelona tío
this is good for your string to do
esto está bien para tu string para hacer
thanks as far as I know to tell you a
las gracias yo que sepa para hacerte una
story something to sleep in maybe
historia algo para dormir a lo mejor
these clothes are also for sleeping but
esta ropa es también para dormir pero
for the Palau de la Msica in Barcelona
para el palau de la música de barcelona
man it
tío
would be Nancy you can interpret it
sería el nancy lo podéis interpretar
nobody is perfect perfect come on let's
nadie es perfecto perfecto vamos vamos a
do it guys all together this mic
hacer los chicos todos juntos este micro
over here let it start let it start they're
por aquí a que empiece que empiecen los
throwing some already cosco this
están tirando unas ya cosco esto me
seems to me sincerely one of the most
parece sinceramente de las cosas más
surreal things in history for what you
surrealistas de la historia para lo
've heard like I said come on if we are
habéis oído como he dicho vamos si
okay 3 2 1 3
vale 3 2 1 3
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music]
[Música]
your [ __ ] mother
tu [__] madre
the award for the best game of the year is
el premio el mejor en juego del año es
attentive Agustn 51
atento agustín 51
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
for which of the tantrums is he late the
por cuál de los enfados sale tarde lo
last one a prize they
último un premio
are giving to last one a prize for
le están dando a último un premio por
getting angry and throwing [ __ ]
enfadarse y tirar [__]
at tortilla
a tortilla
this day they are going on and sister
este día nos andan y sister
the anger that is the one that the one that
el enfado que es el que el que el que la
messed it up because of tortilla
lió por lo de tortilla
because of that anger
por ese enfado
he gets angry no seriously
él se enfada no en serio
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music] it's
[Música]
crazy that the first award of my
manda güevos que el primer premio de mi
life is this
vida sea esto
send egg pasta and well
manda pastas de huevos y bueno por
finally to say that the content that I
último decir que el contenido que más
enjoy the most I am not in tortilla land
disfruto yo no estoy en tortilla land
because it does not come out of the brand cata
porque no me sale de la marca cata
man in general it is because of all the
hombre en general es por todos los
anger it
enfados
is because of everything in general
es por todo en general
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
of the honors
de los honores
what I do not like about wearing is the
lo que no me gusta de llevar es el
hairstyle because we are always going to erase
peinado para que siempre vamos a borrar
or he does not comb it much maybe not
o no se peina mucho igual no
the award to that I say but wind and
el premio a eso digo yo pero wind y le
wind was winning and the wind will be much better and
wind y el the wind irá mucho mejor y más
funnier the one from the box
gracioso el de la caja
totally wind and
totalmente wind y le ganaba
the wind was winning will be better that one yes it is
el the wind irá mejor a ese sí que le
missing calle
falta calle
rolfi leader of the year that agent max or
rolfi líder del año esa agente max o
ah
ah
everyone
a todo el mundo
the saliva
la saliva
last night because I think I will put on
anoche porque pienso ponerme
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
seriously I
en serio
feel I feel super supported by
siento me siento super arropado por
all the content creators who
todos los creados de contenido que
speak highly of me and I have been
habláis súper bien de mí y llevo muchos
in this for many years and I always felt super
años en esto y siempre me sentía súper
good with you thanks to my friends to
bien con vosotros gracias a mis amigos a
my family and to everyone and for being
mi familia y a todo el mundo y por estar
here
aquí
because I have no idea right now
porque yo no tengo ni idea ahora mismo
clip of the year the in fact new one of the
clip del año el de hecho nuevo del
crash
choque
is the same land ran like a joke
es lo mismo land corrió como una gracia
and thanks it does not have the one of let's  playing is
y gracias no tiene el de vamos a jugar
fun the one with the sodas like
es exista divertido el de los refrescos
this on twitter
así en twitter
I would give the award to the one from alde the one with the
yo le daría el premio al de alde el del
grandfather
abuelo
ar of the grandfather grandfather well we created our
ar del abuelo abuelo bueno creamos lo
own thing
suyo
the clip of the year
el clip del año
2021 goes to sergio kun agero he's going to
2021 va para sergio kun agüero va a
play
jugar
totally total something come on
totalmente total algo vamos
well play
bueno jugar
the anger that ended up getting into the fm
el enfado que terminó metiéndose al fm
of a hater
de un hater
who finished doing the cold hater
que terminó de hacer el frío hater
[Music]
[Música]
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
ah
ah
[Music]
[Música]
or
o
's recorded to god
está grabado al dios
wins an award for something well it didn't happen
gana un premio por algo bien no se dio
[Music]
[Música]
rajoy
rajoy
but it was
pero fue
[Music]
[Música]
and people
y la gente
like
cómo
that is the expert look at my dog
ese es el perito mira mi perrita
[Music]
[Música]
I'm laughing my ass off
me parto el peritaje
after the huge speech you
después de el pedazo de discurso que te
've given me I'm going to ask you a favor
has marcado yo te voy a pedir un favor
could you
tú podrías
just for a second take that
solo durante un segundo quitarte esa
ball out of your mouth and give us one
pelota de la boca y regalarnos un
do it with the ball in your mouth please
hazlo con la bola en la boca por favor
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
doing many years
haciendo muchos años
don't miss the others
no faltes a los demás
I love the one who edited this video the one who
me encanta el que ha editado este vídeo
uploaded this  that a
el que ha subido esto que una
compilation asking for a subscription do
recopilación pidiendo la suscripción
you think they hired people to
tú crees que hayan contratado gente para
wait outside I fill the theater for the
esperar afuera yo llenar el teatro del
event I have my doubts naming
evento yo tengo mis dudas nombrar a
pensive face thinking it is full of
pensativa cara pensando está lleno de
youtubers they are youtubers and family members of
youtubers son youtuber y familiares de
youtube in which they are taking the
youtube en los que están llevando el
theater
teatro
family outside but sure that yes it
familiares fuera pero seguro que sí
really is an award that makes me
de verdad es un premio que me hace
very excited there is a lot of work
muchísima ilusión hay muchísimo trabajo
behind it and that my family is behind me
detrás y que mi familia esté detrás
supporting me that the streams to which I
apoyándome que los streams a los que
respect so much supported me makes me
tanto respeto me respaldó me hace
eternally happy and I live for my
eternamente feliz y vivo para mi
profession and what award they gave to the
profesión y los que premio le dieron al
crash has seen us no what award they
choque nos ha visto no que premio le
gave to chocas
dieron a chocas
stop putting what award will say the
dejar de poner a qué premio le dirá la
choca you
choca
see you are almost 30 years old
ya ver que ya tienes casi 30 años la
half of what you have grandpa javi hehe
mitad de lo que tienes abuelo javi jeje
and the award to dallas for the youtuber with the
y el premio a dallas por el youtuber con
most money donated of the 10 thousand bitcoins
más dinero donado de los 10 mil bitcoin
better is first the crash
mejor es primero el choque
better be m
mejor esté m
to the revelation
a la revelación
well but for me it would have been me juan
bien pero para mí hubiera sido yo juan
for me it has been juan that the grace is
para mí ha sido juan que la gracia es
fair that there are people like you who
justo que haya gente como tú que se lo
take everything too seriously and are made of
toma todo demasiado en serio y es de
glass you are cannon fodder for these
cristal eres carne de cañón para esta
people you are 40 years old brother stop  you're
gente tienes 40 años hermano deja de ser
so boring you're not funny or have any
tan aburrido no tienes gracia ni
content of your own and that's why you just limit yourself to
contenido propio y por eso te limitas a
commenting
comentar
now but you'll probably earn the same as
ya pero seguramente cobre lo mismo que
your father in two years in a month he knows but do
tu padre en dos años en un mes sabe pero
n't make so many friends you don't know who
no te hagas tanto amigos no sabes quién
you are his
eres
name is Javi you're pathetic
se ha puesto de nombre javi das pena
because we'll have it okay now the chat is
porque lo habremos vale ahora el chat
challenging the whole level let's try
safía de todo el nivel trate vamos a
hygiene
higiene
or so
o sea eso
a kid who's not Spanish okay he's a
un chaval que no es español vale es un
kid who is Spanish and look how much
chaval que es español y fíjate lo que se
has burned how much has burned I mean you have
ha ardido
n't
lo que se ha ardido o sea no habéis
banned many people there right now you don't
baneado mucha gente hay de ahora no
know banned three people more or
sabéis baneado a tres personas más o
less no matter three people more or less well
menos no sea tres personas más o menos
one of those three is so angry and
pues uno de esos tres está tan rabioso y
can't stand you getting involved and
no pueda aguantar que te metas y que
criticizing his YouTube and like the
critiques a su youtube y como las
chat ways aire he spent a
maneras del chat aire se ha gastado un
euro to do it like that and he didn't even
euro para hacerlo así y ni siquiera la
want to do it like with his name and I
quería hacer como con su nombre y
bet Javi you're pathetic
apuesto javi das pena
really you've just left me all
de verdad que ya me acabas de dejar todo
scratched dude
rayado tío
really now he's just left me all
de verdad que ahora me acaba de dejar
scratched dude you
todo rayado tío
've already hurt me friend you've left me
ya me has hecho daño amigo me has dejado
terrible the whole chat is with you  long
fatal todo el chat está contigo
live the joints
vivan los porros
or not
o no
and on top of that it will have pissed him off
y encima y encima le habrá [__]
spending the euro on the worst and doing
gastarse el euro de lo peor y haciendo
for every friend
para todo amigo
you have won Islam the very
has ganado el islam los clips muy
characteristic clips you could shut up
característicos podrías mandar a callar
everyone who is watching us with
a todo el mundo que nos está viendo con
a small gesture of yours because
un pequeño gesto de los tuyos porque
which is our camera
cuál es nuestra cámara
talking
hablando
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
and the winner of the talk show of the year
y el ganador al talk show del año
is the show
está el show
el tacho obviously without a doubt
el tacho evidentemente sin ninguna duda
without a doubt without a doubt to
sin ninguna duda sin ninguna duda a
Jordi White
jordi white
but come on without a doubt there is no
pero vamos sin ninguna duda no hay
competition there is no competition it is not
competencia no hay competencia no es
anger for the awards and especially for
enfado por los premios y sobre todo por
the song from before and all because it is that
la canción de antes y tal porque es que
the wild project won
lo ha ganado the wild project
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music]
[Música]
but without a doubt the way it is the roll
pero sin duda la manera se lo el rollo
that the treatment has it, I mean the best it
que lleva el trato o sea la mejor
would be good if there was an award for the
estaría bueno que hubiera un premio al
internet or also because
internet o también porque se le rompió
a tooth broke on someone, that would be the last straw, as
un diente a uno ya ya sería el colmo ya
for the awards, first of all
de los premios primero de todo muchas
thank you very much
gracias
I like the gala a lot it is very well
me gusta la gala mucho de estar muy bien
done it is very professional apart from a
hecha está muy profesional quitando un
couple of little details very professional very
par de detallitos muy profesional muy
professional it seems that it has been organized by
profesional parece que han organizado
people who have been doing
gente que llevan toda la vida haciendo
this type of thing all their lives and I think that  this
este tipo de cosas y yo creo que este
award is for the case of the people
premio es para el caso de la gente
still certain thing and that is the
todavía cierta cosa y que es la
contracted clear really is the award
contratado claro realmente es el premio
for a content although change and jordi
a un contenido aunque cambio y jordi
gual the site for the internet for the
gual el sitio para en internet para el
content as of equal but I know that
contenido como de igual pero yo sé que
a content where people get wet
un contenido donde la gente se moja
where they talk about complicated topics sometimes
donde se habla de temas complicados a
[Music]
[Música]
but I
pero
was about to be
estuve a punto de ser
killed by pablo escobar we have to
asesinado por pablo escobar tenemos para
save ourselves with txiki if I leave they will kick me out
salvarnos con txiki si me vaya me van a
of trichet 15 20 million
echar de trichet 15 20 millones de
visits for 260 literally it
visitas por 260 literalmente
is a type of salsa it
es un tipo de salsa
is a type of salt or people
es un tipo de sal se o la gente se le
believe that it is the senama that is salz the
cree que es el senama que es salz el
youtube be I would recommend to
youtube sea yo le recomendaría a la
people that watch the scam video this one
gente que mira el vídeo de estafa este
that made of the good bad salsero and will
que hizo del salsero bueno malo y
understand that the salsero clear here what
entenderá que el salsero claro aquí lo
happens in spain that the birth of the
que pasa en españa que el nacimiento el
salsero was made by nacho salsero youtuber
salsero lo hizo nacho salsero youtuber
okay then clear l'infiestu that I don't know
vale entonces claro l'infiestu que no sé
why he had so many hate brasilia of the
por qué tenía tantos hate brasilia de la
face a little that the salsero garcia
cara un poco que el salsero garcía
salcedo I had property that it was not either  it
salcedo tuve propiedad de que tampoco
wasn't harmful they have become salsa
era no era dañino se han hecho de salsa
youtuber people threw a lot of hate at him and
youtuber la gente le echaba mucho hate y
the only thing he did was clear is the month and
lo único que hacía era claro es el mes y
see the one who gave a bad image to the salsa singer
ver al que dio mala imagen al salsero
really be because Nacho comes out
realmente sea porque nacho sale
literally tell you what happened in
literalmente contarte lo que pasaba en
two minutes period I didn't even give my opinion
dos minutos punto ni opinaba
read tweets look at this
leer tweets mira este
point
punto
and people threw hate at him he said but what
y la gente le tiraba hate dijo pero qué
's wrong with what he does
tiene de malo lo que hace
understand me that he has bad wishes there are
me entiende que tiene malos deseos son
many things salcedo it is anything
muchas cosas salcedo es cualquier cosa
that is controversial it may have come out
que sea polémica puede haber salido
even video games it may have been because it is
hasta los videojuegos puede haberse al
such and then the slam awards
ser tal y entonces los premios slam
these will be complete the year they
estos estarán completos el año que le
put the salsa category because it is
metan la categoría del salsero porque es
a category more
una categoría más
award the best the
premio el mejor
best salt channel ceo because now
el mejor canal de sal ceo porque ahora
category more
categoría más
then when I accept it is in politics it
entonces cuando acepte es en la política
is to the pse or politics and many
es al pse o la política y muchísimos al
being
ser
many to the pse or in what series of these
muchísimos al pse o en qué serie de esta
people of which they make tortilla
gente de la que hacen de tortilla la
denied it I don't know that there is no salt or if it is that
negó la no sé que no hay sal se o si es
the salsero what moves it
que el salsero lo que lo mueve
but that is well left active many
pero eso nos bien queda activo mucha
many people not that the salsa
mucha gente no es que el salsa
the content of this is not half
el contenido de éste no lo medio
controversial I don't know that it is not worth
polémica no sé que no vale
but it is that within our  series
pero es que dentro de nuestras series
you talk to 66 to the ceo no then jordi
habláis al 66 al ceo no entonces jordi
while same jordi way same
while mismo jordi way mismo
did something super and
hizo una cosa súper y propiedad
hypocritical property the other day that we were
hipócrita del otro día que lo estuvimos
watching it
viendo
was when the punch to dario that was
fue cuando lo del puñetazo a darío que
put on one of those channels I don't know if he
se puso en uno de esos canales no sé si
said [ __ ]
dijo de [__] inventando
effectively inventing in the 200 channels
efectivamente en los 200 canales
then to the shitty guy finally
entonces al señor de [__] arma por fin
gave something like that no
dio algo así no
800 channels that have uploaded and have
800 canales que han subido y han
commented on the click of dario's punch
comentado el clic del puñetazo de darío
m milk no and now he had two videos
m leche no y ahora él tenía dos vídeos
talking about dario's punch from ph and the thing
hablando del puñetazo de darío de ph y
is that all this content is salsa in a
es que todo este contenido es salsero en
way it takes
cierto modo
a guy who almost the need
se lleva a un tío que casi la necesidad
pablo escobar takes it very free to
pablo escobar se lleva muy libre para
talk to them about the nfc of the coins they do not
hablarles de los nfc de las monedas no
stay as soon as they are salt or loves
se quedan en cuanto son sal se o amores
to the pse or the heart it is not to the ceo of
al pse o del corazón no es al ceo de
youtube it is not the ceret to the salsero everything
youtube no es el céret al salsero todo
that is salsa rich salsa let's
lo que sea salsa salsa rica
see salsa it is not an interview they are not
a ver salsero no es entrevista no son
interviews they
entrevistas
are talks it is not it is not they are not interviews
son charlas no es no es no son
interviews other things are talks
entrevistas otras cosas son charlas
me  you understand
me entendéis
30 thousand dollars then knowing crazy
30 mil dólares entonces saber una locura
those months in fact it is not a
esos meses de hecho no es ninguna
song I'm sorry those who sing for
canción lo siento los que cantan de
real because he turned it into a
verdad porque él lo convirtió en una
song he
canción
has balls and I take it like a [ __ ]
tiene [__] y lo llevo de [__] madre
of this so much is there all the time with
de ésta tanto está todo el rato ahí con
the subject and toxicity out and the truth is
el tema y toxicidad fuera y la verdad
that I remember him with great affection
que lo recuerdo con con gran cariño
thank you very much lucas is a crack
muchas gracias lucas es un crack
applause
aplauso
please santo and the honors of the
por favor santo y los honores de la
community vote and the extremes
votación de la comunidad y los extremos
okay let's go
okay let's go
sport player of the year
jugador de sport del año
completely good idea
completamente buena idea
[Music]
[Música]
and daddy gabi is a very good person I
y es que papi gabi es buenísima persona
tell you at the beginning the person
te lo digo al inicio la persona
and fun already daddy I met him in person I have
y divertido ya papi lo conocí en persona
told him sometimes how much time I had
lo he contado alguna vez lo mucho tiempo
with him
con él
right now where would be the photo
ahora mismo dónde estaría la foto
to the interview I did with him he destroyed
a la entrevista que le hice de destrozó
a comment and you limit yourself to
en un comentario y te limitas a
responding saying that you earn more than me
responder diciendo que ganas más que yo
and my parents it
y mis padres
shows the shame it remains like that how much
demuestra la pena queda así lo mucho que
you know that you are not capable of entertaining
sabes que no eres capaz de entretener
by yourself and you refer to commenting on
por ti solo y te remites a comentar
other people's content is
contenido de otros
worth two thousand viewers 2 thousand
vale dos mil espectadores 2 mil
viewers in this right in
espectadores en este derecho en el de
the afternoon talking about the heart six
por la tarde hablando del corazón seis
thousand how many have their dances of another
mil cuántos tienen sus danzas de otro
euro  and you tell me or not better yet
euro y me lo dices o no mejor aún
turn up the call turn up to beat
sube la llamada sube de batir
the debated now he came in and thinks he
los debatido ahora entraba y cree que
'll go up he thinks his life is screwed but the interview he does in papilla has been around for years now that he sings forward he wasn't even known to bite well when you say interviews vera he wasn't even known to piray of you he has my interview four years ago it has three thousand visits in 2017 the papiro channel
en el 2017 el canal de papiro
has the channel because a person who
tiene el canal porque una persona que
passes head we are here to interview him
pasa cabeza estamos acá a entrevistarle
again to bite well I'm
otra vez para picar bien
going to tell him to see if to bite and
se lo voy a decir a ver si a picar y que
come to throw it
venga a echarla
being a motorcycle not to do you have or you have
siendo una moto no hacer tengas o tienes
some tender you know the work that
algún tierno sabéis el trabajado que
was this interview tion you
eran esta entrevista ción
don't know the work in this interview
no sabéis el trabajar en esta entrevista
the edition - it depends
la edición
I'm noticing 53 thousand subscribers I had
estoy notando 53 mil suscriptores tenía
to bite and here I
para picar y aquí
upload whenever you want now please right now right now
subo cuando quieras ahora por favor
please right
ahora mismo por favor
now tell me you
ahora mismo dime tú
tell me a stringer link good how do we
dime un enlace de stringer bueno como lo
do it to connect because if I
hacemos para conectar porque si te
was hiding you without putting your name
estaba ocultando sin poner tu nombre
how do we do it
como lo hacemos
how do we do it put me
cómo lo hacemos
your album put me
ponme tu disco
your album please
ponme tu disco por fa
and I'll add you and  you accept me
y te agrego y tú me acepta a mí
to see the photo that I had with daddy
a ver la foto que yo tenía con papi
lip of this one
labia de ésta
that I want you to see me with porridge well we
que quiero que me veáis con papilla bien
do it
lo hacemos
ay
ay
Haiti with daddy
haití con papi
well what a young floor option well
bien que joven suelos opción pues hace
five years of this
cinco años de esto
what jacket is
qué chaqueta está
what jacket is a blue jacket I don't
qué chaqueta está una chaqueta azul
even know what jacket it is
no sé ni qué chaqueta es
okay okay
vale vale
yes annoying that Javier is all what you
que si pesado que javier es todo lo que
say but he is in
dices pero él todos los días está
front of thousands of people every day and
delante de miles de personas y nos
entertains us I'm sure it pisses you off that I tell
entretiene seguro que te jode que diga
the truth about the youtubers that you like
la verdad de los youtubers que te gustan
and you're crying long live the churra
y andas llorando viva el churra
no but they warned me something Paulo
no pero me han avisado una cosilla paulo
warned me something that he's right do
me avisa una cosilla que tiene razón
n't pay him any more attention new balls leave him
no le deis más bola nuevas bolas dejarle
that the money no why I'll
que el dinero no por qué
say it tomorrow remember tomorrow the day after remind me tomorrow the day
ya lo diré mañana acordarme mañana
after let him tell us
recordarme mañana pasado que nos diga el
why
porqué
although well we could be careful and that's it no I don't
aunque bueno podríamos tener cuidado y
know I don't know if but it's
punto no no sé no sé si pero
already explained because you can't okay okay ignore ignore
ya se explicó porque no puedes vale vale
him
pasar de pasar de él
good for nibbling on wines which is very good to
bueno para picar vinos que es muy bien a
everyone
todos
[Music]
[Música]
the nominees
los nominados
please whenever you want gorgeous ua
por favor cuando quieras guapísima ua
bitter prison dance of the year is for
prisión amarga baile del año es para
those who  nominated and it's going to be good
quienes a los nominado y va a ir a bueno
but daddy without a doubt and dj mario
pero papi sin duda y dj mario
okay yes yes yes wants to go up let it go
vale sí sí sí quiere subir que suba de
up
suba
for pillay
para pillay
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music]
[Música]
just want to say something before I
simplemente quiere decir algo antes de
go and hits
irme y éxitos
[Music]
[Música]
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
more is missing now
más falta lo de ahora
allows me from position I'm going to give a
me permite de posición voy a hacer un
gift well
regalo bueno
no this is a filter an
no esto es un filtro un filtro de
internet filter or so you can do whatever you
internet o para que te hagas tú lo que
want the espe
quieras la espe
okay at 15 what's going on
vale al 15 qué pasa
here we have it in call a law
aquí lo tenemos en llamada una ley en
seriously well first here they are
serio pues primero aquí se están
calling each other a [ __ ] they have called you
llamando a un [__] te han llamado
host the many threats tortilla damn
[__] el muchísimo amagos tortilla [__]
ah
ah
I eat to one change the rubber on the
yo como a uno le cambia la goma al
microphone every week
micrófono cada semana
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
hey now you hear me I
oye ahora me escuchas
hear perfectly that they were like this it
escucho perfecto que eran como esto no
will not be a video it is not strange that he had
será un vídeo no es raro que tuvo
a live PCR no I already did that
una pcr en directo no eso ya lo hice yo
and I do not recommend it the truth is I do not
y no te lo recomiendo la verdad no te lo
recommend it much yet how next
recomiendo mucho aún como de siguiente
getting author let's see your scholarship is fasting from
sacando autor a ver tu beca se ayuna de
antigen which is from the stick
antígeno que es de el palito
there is one of antigen which is with the stick
hay una de antígeno que es con el palito
I say wow
digo vaya telita
I am not  able to get into it as much as
yo no soy capaz de meterme lo tanto como
a great project
un gran proyecto
I feel with Kobe but very happy the
me siento con kobe pero muy contento la
truth is it is a project to which we exposed
verdad es un proyecto al que expusimos
a lot of love and hey, what does it look like
mucho cariño y oye que se ve así
recognized, the truth is that I am disgusting,
reconocido la verdad es que yo qué asco
the truth is that I need very proud
la verdad es que necesito muy orgulloso
look man,
mira tío
in trauma, life today in Draw My Life is
en trauma la vida hoy en draw my life es
the CNDH I will be brief yesterday
la cndh seré breve ayer se celebraron
the awards were held they are organized by
los premios están organizados por
decree in order to reward and
decreto con el fin de premiar y
recognize the work of the best
reconocer el trabajo de los mejores
Spanish-speaking streamers of 2021
streamers hispanohablantes del 2021
truce at seven thirty everything was
tregua por las siete y media todo estaba
perfectly arranged in the Palau de
perfectamente dispuesto en el palau de
la Msica in Barcelona with a red carpet
la música de barcelona con alfombra roja
and everything the gala had more than a
y todo la gala contó con más de un
million viewers at its
millón de espectadores en su punto
peak it tasted very good, very good, but as I
álgido supo muy bien la muy bien pero ya
say, when it has a category it goes
lo digo cuando tenga una categoría pasa
to SEO then and waiting of course for
al seo entonces y esperando desde luego
the Golden Globes and placing itself as the
los globos de oro y colocándose como el
third most viewed stream, the first
tercer stream más visto el primero
also belongs to the serious and the second
pertenece también al grave y el segundo
to Ibai with the boxing evening let's go with
a ibai con la velada de boxeo vamos con
the winners and best moments
los ganadores y mejores momentos
thanks to you ask me what I thought
gracias a ti me pregunta que me pareció
you are as a presenter very good,
eres como presentador muy bien
very good, very good, very good, very good,
muy bien muy bien muy bien muy bien
very good, he did very well
muy bien muy bien lo hizo muy bien
points  from island it all started with the
puntos de island todo comenzó con el
award for best clip of the year which was
premio al mejor clip del año que fue
given to kun for his well let's
entregado al kun por su bueno vamos a
play the one well while drinking some
jugar el uno bueno mientras tomaba un
water he started talking about the explosion
agüita comenzó a hablar de la explosión
of the book of 2020 and then let out his
del libro de 2020 para después soltar su
well let's play the former soccer player
bueno vamo a jugá el exfutbolista no
could not attend the gala but connected
pudo acudir a la gala pero se conectó
to thank him next came the
para agradecerlo a continuación vino el
feil of the year which could not be for anyone other
feil del año que no podía ser para otro
than ibai due to the moment at the
que para ibai debido al momento en los
40 music awards when he covered the
40 music awards cuando tapó a los
luxury spectators between rosala and
espectadores de lujo entre rosalía y
rabo alejandro not even wanting to could have
rabo alejandro ni queriendo podría
done it better the anger of the year
haberlo hecho mejor el enfado del año
was close but it was at ease
estaba reñido pero fue a gustito
account and one who won the trophy
cuenta y uno quien se alzó con el trofeo
thanks to his attack against and I open
gracias a su ataque contra y abro
quotes the kids who watch tortilla
comillas los niñatos que ven tortilla
land
land
unbelievable that they gave him an award
increíble que le hayan dado un premio
for that it
por eso de
is incredible
es increíble
incredible
increíble
v0 rsh numeral
v0 rsh numeral
8.453 let's
8.453
see paulo write down how quickly write down what
a ver paulo apunta lo rápido apunta lo
paula and quickly that we are going to add it
paula y rápido que lo vamos a agregar
now
ahora
paula supported send it to me by waza
apuntaló paula mandámelo por waza
then for picadita not the
después para picadita no el baile del
new year's dance agent max or obtained the  award
año nuevo agente max o obtuvo el premio
for 'best realplayer' by his fans in
al 'mejor realplayer por sus hinchas en
gta 5 that he deserved the award he made it
gta 5 que merecía el galardón lo dejó
clear when giving his
claro al dar su discurso de
acceptance speech continuing with his
agradecimiento siguiendo con su
character
personaje
maxwell won the award for best
maxwell ganó el premio al mejor jugador
iu esports player christine and not even best
de iu esports christine y ni a mejor
reporter of the year in i esports and kak
reportera del año en i esports y kaká
yes christine and this year she has not been the
si christine y este año ya no ha sido el
report it was not
reporte era no
christina and this year she has been a reporter
christina y este año ha sido reportera
christina starts in the been a reporter
christina inicia en el sido reportera
the best caster of the year these two were
la mejor caster del año estas dos fueron
the only women awarded let's see
las únicas mujeres premiadas venga a ver
if it goes in next year sequels well
si va en el año que viene secuelas bueno
streamer more
streamer más
but what does it matter if they are women or
pero que importa que sean mujeres o que
men within the category what there is
sean hombres dentro de la categoría lo
to what there is man for me is
que hay a lo que hay hombre para mí es
anger should have won not
del enfado lo tenía que haber ganado ni
satcher
satcher
the best is first and rl was that it did not
el mejor es primer y rl fue que no nos
surprise us wind the wind as you well know
sorprendió wind the wind como bien sabes
was more than 700 hours live
estuvo más de 700 horas en directo
visiting different spanish streamers
visitando diferentes streamers españoles
very much at the level of the greats it happens to you trade
muy a la altura de los grandes te ocurre
winds of television and speaking of
alisios de la televisión y hablando de
television content the wild project
contenido de televisión the wild project
won best talk show for its
ganó mejor talk show por su formato de
interview format and we go again with  ibai
entrevistas y vamos de nuevo con ibai
who won best song of the year with the
que ganó a mejor canción del año con el
ibai quartet along with luca requena
cuarteto de ibai junto con luca requena
with whom he collected the award and horta to
con quien recogió el premio y horta para
see that award is won by luca requena
ver a ese premio lo gana luca requena
right well and since we're at it let's go with
verdad bueno y ya que estamos vamos con
the rest of the awards that he won and vai
el resto de premios que ganó y vai
won the award for event of the year
obtuvo el galardón a el evento del año
with the boxing evening although he
con la velada de boxeo aunque también
was also nominated for other suspended
estaba nominado por otros de suspendidos
events and the best award tell me and
eventos y el premio mejores dime y es
as he said now if anyone deserves
que como dijo ahora si alguien se merece
that award it's you I arrived in his
ese premio ese eres tú llegue en su
own category jager of the year he won
propia categoría de jager del año ganó
with his jagger boxer he received the award
con su jagger boxeador recibió el premio
with a black ball in his mouth he was competing
con una bola negra en la boca competía
with andiamo a teacher trip and arrive
con andiamo un profesor viaje y llegar
princess fernn blood won the award for
princesa fernán blood ganó el premio a
best career for his great work
la mejor trayectoria por su gran trabajo
over the years he was not at the
a lo largo de los años no estuvo en la
gala but he sent a video thanking for the
gala pero mandó un vídeo agradeciendo el
award another who could not attend the
galardón otro que no pudo acudir al
palau de la msica went where but he
palau de la música fue a dónde pero se
connected live to collect his
conectó en directo para recoger su
award for tortilla the cndh el chocas and
premio por tortilla la cndh el chocas y
his 1,500 euro suit won the
su traje de 1.500 euros ganaron el
revelation streamer award because  One
premio streamer revelación porque
thousand five hundred euros the active clash is not
mil quinientos euros el choque activa no
the best suit I
es el mejor traje
don't like this you can have the
esto no me gusta puedes tener los
prizes yesterday they seemed fair to you okay
premios ayer te parecieron justos vale
great friends I did like them but I
genial amigos a mí sí me gustaron pero
insist and put pressure on you with this
insisto y meter presión ustedes con esto
too man it has been done if not the week
también tío se ha hecho sino la semana
between everything is missing a category well
entre todo sea falta una categoría bueno
one or two categories for the salsero like that no not
una o dos categoría para el salsero así
everyone is represented in the
no no está representado todo el mundo de
string world okay
los string vale